Guide to the Viola F. Barnes Photograph Collection Documenting Life at Yale
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Viola F. Barnes photograph collection documenting life at Yale
1916-1919
RU 660
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.25
The materials consist of photographs documenting Viola Barnes's (Yale 1919 PhD) student life at Yale and in New Haven. Included are photographs of fellow women graduate students, friends, outings, and activities.
Barnes, Viola Florence, 1885-1979
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 48-A (YRG 48-A), Yale pictorial records and collections.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
Arranged by subject.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of photographs documenting Viola Barnes's (Yale 1919 PhD) student life at Yale and in New Haven. Included are photographs of fellow women graduate students, friends, outings, and activities.
New Haven (Conn.) -- Pictorial works; Photographs; Barnes, Viola Florence, 1885-1979; Yale University -- Pictorial works; Yale University -- Students
- Photographs, Series I
  - Viola Barnes in library; graduate student in lab; graduate student in lab with rabbit, circa 1916-1919 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Photos with two people, circa 1916-1919 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Outing in the hills, circa 1916-1919 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Reunion parade, circa 1916-1919 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Two houses, circa 1916-1919 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - New Haven and vicinity, circa 1916-1919 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - ROTC on Old Campus, circa 1916-1919 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - World War I activities on the New Haven Green, circa 1916-1919 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Lighthouse Point, circa 1916-1919 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Yale Bowl, circa 1916-1919 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Individuals, circa 1916-1919 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Group photos, circa 1916-1919 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - People in a library, circa 1916-1919 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Beach outings, circa 1916-1919 (Box 1, Folder 14 - 15)
  - Graduation, circa 1916-1919 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Yale scenes, circa 1916-1919 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Annotated envelopes to be used in aiding identification, circa 1916-1919 (Box 1, Folder 18)